Where hope survives.
Beyond Borders is a drama, romance, adventure film directed by Martin Campbell.
Sarah Jordan, an American living in London in 1984, is married
to the son of a wealthy British industrialist.
She encounters Nick Callahan, a renegade doctor, whose impassioned plea for help
to support his relief efforts in war-torn Africa moves her deeply.
As a result, Sarah embarks upon a journey of discovery that leads to
danger, heartbreak and romance in the far corners of the world.
Sarah Jordan, played by Angelina Jolie.
Nick Callahan, played by Clive Owen.
Charlotte Jordan, played by Teri Polo.
Henry Bauford, played by Linus Roache.
Elliott Hauser, played by Noah Emmerich.
Steiger, played by Yorick van Wageningen.
Beyond Borders is a 2003 American romantic-drama film about aid workers, directed by  Martin
Campbell and starring Angelina Jolie, Clive Owen, Teri Polo and Kate Ashfield.
The original music score was composed by James Horner.
Reflecting Jolie's real-life interest in promoting humanitarian relief,
the film was critically and financially unsuccessful.
The film was marketed with the tagline "In a place she didn't belong, among people she never knew, she found a way to make a difference."
Concurrently with the release of the film, Jolie published Notes from My
Travels, a collection of journal entries from her real-life experiences as a Goodwill Ambassador for the United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees (UNHCR) — similar to her character in the film.
The film explores themes of london, england, central intelligence
agency (cia), cambodia, love of one's life, landmine.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.